(this["webpackJsonpflash-card-generator"]=this["webpackJsonpflash-card-generator"]||[]).push([[0],{15:function(e,t,r){e.exports={navbar:"Layout_navbar__2Jj_v",logo:"Layout_logo__2c34V",menu:"Layout_menu__7RCvq",footer:"Layout_footer__7ZyTp"}},19:function(e,t,r){e.exports={btn:"Button_btn__1Lkv5",btnPrimary:"Button_btnPrimary__g_WP5",btnSecondary:"Button_btnSecondary__1e7dV"}},21:function(e,t,r){e.exports={formGroup:"Form_formGroup__1ZK03",formLabel:"Form_formLabel__3fysd"}},3:function(e,t,r){e.exports={cardBuilder:"CardBuilder_cardBuilder__1-TML",cardsContainer:"CardBuilder_cardsContainer__2s9qv",formContainer:"CardBuilder_formContainer__2U-SC",submitContainer:"CardBuilder_submitContainer__3R_1h",submitBtn:"CardBuilder_submitBtn__2wJQP",previewBtn:"CardBuilder_previewBtn__1ROgs",cardItem:"CardBuilder_cardItem__3Yw7o",btnContainer:"CardBuilder_btnContainer__eyOUg",editIcon:"CardBuilder_editIcon__ej095",deleteIcon:"CardBuilder_deleteIcon__2tKgj",cardFront:"CardBuilder_cardFront__2ZsvS",cardBack:"CardBuilder_cardBack__30C_h",cardBody:"CardBuilder_cardBody__eKxsl",previewModal:"CardBuilder_previewModal__2qUqN",previewContainer:"CardBuilder_previewContainer__1t0z1",editModal:"CardBuilder_editModal__20SRu",editContainer:"CardBuilder_editContainer__kOgiO",formGroup:"CardBuilder_formGroup__20Zns"}},33:function(e,t,r){e.exports={layout:"LandingPage_layout__sZx6f"}},39:function(e,t,r){},50:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var n=r(25),a=r.n(n),c=(r(39),r(11)),o=r(4),i=r(15),s=r.n(i),d=r(1),l=function(){return Object(d.jsx)("footer",{className:s.a.footer,children:Object(d.jsx)("small",{children:"\xa9 Copyright 2021, David Beer"})})},j=function(){return Object(d.jsxs)("nav",{className:s.a.navbar,children:[Object(d.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/",className:s.a.logo,children:"hedgeyCards"}),Object(d.jsxs)("ul",{className:s.a.menu,children:[Object(d.jsx)("li",{children:Object(d.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/",children:"Home"})}),Object(d.jsx)("li",{children:Object(d.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/create",children:"Create"})}),Object(d.jsx)("li",{children:Object(d.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/#contact",children:"Contact"})})]})]})},u=function(e){var t=e.children;return Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)(j,{}),t,Object(d.jsx)(l,{})]})},b=r(27),f=r.n(b),O=r(16),x=r(30),h=r(10),m=r(2),p=r(14),_=r(12),v=r(21),C=r.n(v),B=function(e){var t=e.children;return Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:C.a.formGroup,children:t})},k=function(e){var t=e.children,r=e.inputID;return Object(d.jsx)("label",{className:C.a.formLabel,htmlFor:r,children:t})},g=r(51),y=r(3),N=r.n(y),F=function(e){var t=e.addCardToStack,r=Object(m.useState)({id:"",front:"",back:"",footerFront:"",footerBack:""}),n=Object(h.a)(r,2),a=n[0],c=n[1],o=Object(m.useRef)(null);function i(e){c(Object(_.a)(Object(_.a)({},a),{},Object(p.a)({},e.target.name,e.target.value)))}return Object(d.jsxs)("form",{onSubmit:function(e){e.preventDefault();var r=Object(_.a)(Object(_.a)({},a),{},{id:Object(g.a)()});t(r),c({id:"",front:"",back:"",footerFront:"",footerBack:""}),o.current&&o.current.focus()},className:N.a.formContainer,children:[Object(d.jsxs)(B,{children:[Object(d.jsx)(k,{inputID:"front",children:"Front"}),Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",name:"front",id:"front",value:a.front,ref:o,onChange:function(e){return i(e)},required:!0})]}),Object(d.jsxs)(B,{children:[Object(d.jsx)(k,{inputID:"back",children:"Back"}),Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",name:"back",id:"back",value:a.back,onChange:function(e){return i(e)},required:!0})]}),Object(d.jsxs)(B,{children:[Object(d.jsx)(k,{inputID:"footerFront",children:"Footer Front"}),Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",name:"footerFront",id:"footerFront",value:a.footerFront,onChange:function(e){return i(e)}})]}),Object(d.jsxs)(B,{children:[Object(d.jsx)(k,{inputID:"footerFront",children:"Footer Back"}),Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",name:"footerBack",id:"footerBack",value:a.footerBack,onChange:function(e){return i(e)}})]}),Object(d.jsx)("span",{className:N.a.submitContainer,children:Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"submit",value:" + ",className:N.a.submitBtn})})]})},S=r(22),w=r(31),I=function(e){var t=e.card,r=e.deleteCard,n=e.populateEditModal;return Object(d.jsxs)("li",{className:N.a.cardItem,children:[Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:N.a.cardFront,onClick:function(){return n(t.id,!1)},children:[Object(d.jsx)("p",{className:N.a.cardBody,children:t.front}),t.footerFront?Object(d.jsx)("small",{className:N.a.cardFooter,children:t.footerFront}):null]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:N.a.cardBack,onClick:function(){return n(t.id,!1)},children:[Object(d.jsx)("p",{className:N.a.cardBody,children:t.back}),t.footerBack?Object(d.jsx)("small",{className:N.a.cardFooter,children:t.footerBack}):null]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:N.a.btnContainer,children:[Object(d.jsx)(w.a,{className:N.a.editIcon,onClick:function(){return n(t.id,!1)}}),Object(d.jsx)(S.b,{className:N.a.deleteIcon,onClick:function(){return r(t.id)}})]})]})},P=function(e){var t=e.cardStack,r=e.deleteCard,n=e.populateEditModal;return Object(d.jsx)("section",{className:N.a.cardList,children:Object(d.jsx)("ul",{children:t.map((function(e){return Object(d.jsx)(I,{card:e,deleteCard:r,populateEditModal:n},e.id)}))})})},L=r(19),D=r.n(L),J=function(e){var t=e.children,r=e.type,n=e.isPrimary,a=e.onClick;function c(){a&&a()}return n?Object(d.jsx)("button",{className:"".concat(D.a.btn," ").concat(D.a.btnPrimary),type:r,onClick:function(){return c()},children:t}):Object(d.jsx)("button",{className:"".concat(D.a.btn," ").concat(D.a.btnSecondary),type:r,onClick:function(){return c()},children:t})},E=r(32),M=r.n(E),T=r(6),G=r.n(T),R=function(e){var t=e.id,r=e.cardSide,n=e.isFront,a=e.withBorder;return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:a?Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:G.a.card,children:Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"".concat(G.a.cardBody),children:Object(d.jsx)("p",{children:n?r.front:r.back})})},t):Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:G.a.card,children:Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:G.a.cardBody,children:Object(d.jsx)("p",{children:n?r.front:r.back})})},t)})},q=function(e){var t=e.togglePreview,r=Object(m.useState)([]),n=Object(h.a)(r,2),a=n[0],c=n[1],o=Object(m.useState)(!1),i=Object(h.a)(o,2),s=i[0],l=(i[1],Object(m.useRef)(null));Object(m.useEffect)((function(){var e=localStorage.getItem("cards");if(null!==e){var t=JSON.parse(e);c(t)}}),[s]);var j=[];return Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:G.a.previewLayout,ref:l,children:[Object(d.jsxs)("header",{children:[Object(d.jsx)(S.a,{className:G.a.modalCloseBtn,onClick:function(){return t()}}),Object(d.jsx)("h1",{children:"Preview"}),Object(d.jsx)("p",{children:"Scroll to see next pages"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:G.a.previewBody,children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:G.a.pageContainer,children:(function(){for(var e=a,t=[],r=e.length;r>0;)if(e.length>=10){var n=[e.splice(0,10)];t=[].concat(Object(O.a)(t),[n[0]]),r-=10}else{var c=[e.splice(0,e.length)];t=[].concat(Object(O.a)(t),[c[0]]),r=0}j=t}(),j.map((function(e){return Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:G.a.preview,children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:G.a.pageInnerContainerFront,children:e.map((function(e){return Object(d.jsx)(R,{id:Object(g.a)(),cardSide:e,isFront:!0,withBorder:s})}))},Object(g.a)()),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:G.a.pageInnerContainerBack,children:e.map((function(e){return Object(d.jsx)(R,{id:Object(g.a)(),cardSide:e,isFront:!1,withBorder:s})}))},Object(g.a)())]},Object(g.a)())})))}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:G.a.previewControls,children:Object(d.jsx)(M.a,{trigger:function(){return Object(d.jsx)(J,{type:"button",isPrimary:!0,children:"Print"})},content:function(){return l.current},documentTitle:"Flash Cards",pageStyle:"margin: 1.2cm 1cm"})})]})]})},Z=function(e){var t=e.cardToEdit,r=e.updateCardStack,n=Object(m.useState)({id:t.id,front:t.front,back:t.back,footerFront:t.footerFront,footerBack:t.footerBack}),a=Object(h.a)(n,2),c=a[0],o=a[1];function i(e){o(Object(_.a)(Object(_.a)({},c),{},Object(p.a)({},e.target.name,e.target.value)))}return Object(d.jsxs)("form",{onSubmit:function(e){e.preventDefault(),r(c,!0),o({id:"",front:"",back:"",footerFront:"",footerBack:""})},className:N.a.editForm,children:[Object(d.jsx)("h3",{children:"EDIT"}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:N.a.formGroup,children:[Object(d.jsx)(k,{inputID:"front",children:"Front"}),Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",name:"front",id:"front",value:c.front,onChange:function(e){return i(e)}})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:N.a.formGroup,children:[Object(d.jsx)(k,{inputID:"back",children:"Back"}),Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",name:"back",id:"back",value:c.back,onChange:function(e){return i(e)}})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:N.a.formGroup,children:[Object(d.jsx)(k,{inputID:"footerFront",children:"Footer Front"}),Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",name:"footerFront",id:"footerFront",value:c.footerFront,onChange:function(e){return i(e)}})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:N.a.formGroup,children:[Object(d.jsx)(k,{inputID:"footerBack",children:"Footer Back"}),Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",name:"footerBack",id:"footerBack",value:c.footerBack,onChange:function(e){return i(e)}})]}),Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"submit",value:"Save"})]})},U=function(){var e=Object(m.useState)((function(){var e=localStorage.getItem("cards");return null!==e&&JSON.parse(e)||[]})),t=Object(h.a)(e,2),r=t[0],n=t[1],a=Object(m.useState)(!1),c=Object(h.a)(a,2),o=c[0],i=c[1],s=Object(m.useState)(!1),l=Object(h.a)(s,2),j=l[0],u=l[1],b=Object(m.useState)({id:"",front:"",back:"",footerFront:"",footerBack:""}),p=Object(h.a)(b,2),_=p[0],v=p[1];function C(){return(C=Object(x.a)(f.a.mark((function e(t){var a;return f.a.wrap((function(e){for(;;)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:0===r.length&&n([t]),a=[].concat(Object(O.a)(r),[t]),localStorage.setItem("cards",JSON.stringify(a)),n(a);case 4:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e)})))).apply(this,arguments)}function B(e){u(!e)}function k(){i(!o)}return Object(m.useEffect)((function(){var e=localStorage.getItem("cards");if(null!==e){var t=JSON.parse(e);n(t)}}),[o,j]),Object(d.jsxs)("main",{className:N.a.cardBuilder,children:[Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:N.a.controls,children:[Object(d.jsx)(F,{addCardToStack:function(e){return function(e){return C.apply(this,arguments)}(e)}}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:N.a.previewBtn,children:Object(d.jsx)(J,{type:"button",isPrimary:!0,onClick:function(){return k()},children:"PREVIEW AND PRINT"})}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:N.a.deleteBtn,children:Object(d.jsx)(J,{type:"button",isPrimary:!1,onClick:function(){return localStorage.setItem("cards",JSON.stringify([])),void n([])},children:"Delete All Cards"})})]}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:N.a.cardsContainer,children:r.length>0?Object(d.jsx)(P,{cardStack:r,deleteCard:function(e){var t=r.filter((function(t){return t.id!==e}));localStorage.setItem("cards",JSON.stringify(t)),n(Object(O.a)(t))},populateEditModal:function(e,t){B(t);var n=r,a=n.findIndex((function(t){return t.id===e}));v(n[a])}}):null}),o?Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:N.a.previewModal,children:Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:N.a.previewContainer,children:Object(d.jsx)(q,{cardStack:r,togglePreview:k})})}):"",j?Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:N.a.editModal,children:Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:N.a.editContainer,children:Object(d.jsx)(Z,{cardToEdit:_,updateCardStack:function(e,t){B(t);var a=r,c=a.findIndex((function(t){return t.id===e.id}));a[c]=e,n(a),localStorage.setItem("cards",JSON.stringify(a)),v({id:"",front:"",back:"",footerFront:"",footerBack:""})}})})}):null]})},V=r(33),K=r.n(V),W=function(){return Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:K.a.layout,children:[Object(d.jsx)("h1",{children:"Under Construction"}),Object(d.jsx)("p",{children:"Check out the builder:"}),Object(d.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/create",children:"Click me!"})]})},A=function(){return Object(d.jsxs)("main",{children:[Object(d.jsx)("h1",{children:"404 - Page Not Found"}),Object(d.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/",children:"Back Home"})]})},H=function(){return Object(d.jsx)(c.a,{children:Object(d.jsx)(u,{children:Object(d.jsxs)(o.c,{children:[Object(d.jsx)(o.a,{exact:!0,path:"/",children:Object(d.jsx)(W,{})}),Object(d.jsx)(o.a,{exact:!0,path:"/create",children:Object(d.jsx)(U,{})}),Object(d.jsx)(o.a,{path:"*",children:Object(d.jsx)(A,{})})]})})})};var z=function(){return Object(d.jsx)(H,{})};a.a.render(Object(d.jsx)(z,{}),document.getElementById("root"))},6:function(e,t,r){e.exports={previewLayout:"Preview_previewLayout__1gWJa",pageInnerContainerFront:"Preview_pageInnerContainerFront__2-VFj",card:"Preview_card__kkkor",cardBody:"Preview_cardBody__TcLJ3",withBorder:"Preview_withBorder__2bkjZ",cardFooter:"Preview_cardFooter__1KTl1",pageInnerContainerBack:"Preview_pageInnerContainerBack__2nb8S",modalCloseBtn:"Preview_modalCloseBtn__3MqEL",previewBody:"Preview_previewBody__1VJa-",pageContainer:"Preview_pageContainer__16UJ5"}}},[[50,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.c8e2b94c.chunk.js.map